rescueme.org 2016-11-01

# Privacy Policy - World Environmental Organization - World.Org

This website is owned by World Environmental Organization, hereinafter referred to as "WEO".

We may change this privacy policy periodically by updating this page. Please check this web page from time to time for changes. Your use of this site following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes.

WEO does not collect any personal information about users, except that which is knowingly and specifically supplied to us by the user.

WEO is committed to ensuring the privacy of your personal information.

WEO will not sell or pass on your information to any other organization outside of WEO unless you specifically and expressly give us permission to do so.

If you are under 18 years old, WEO suggests that you ask your parents or guardian before signing up on this site.

What information do we collect?

a) Personal information such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and date of birth (where appropriate). We collect this information only in connection with specific activities, such as membership, campaigns, feedback, surveys, email newsletter subscriptions, etc. You don't have to disclose any of this information if you do not wish to.

b) Non-personal information such as IP address (the location of the computer on the internet), pages accessed and files downloaded. This helps us to determine how many individuals use our site, how many people visit on a regular basis, which pages are most popular, and which pages are least popular. This information doesn't tell us anything about who you are, it simply allows us to monitor and improve our service.

Personal information submitted through the forms on this site is held only in a WEO database. We promise that WEO will not share the information you give to us on this website with any other organization outside of WEO unless you have specifically given us permission to do so.

If you are under 18, be sure to obtain your parent's or guardian's permission before you send any information about yourself (your name, address, e-mail address, etc.) to us or anyone else over the internet. We encourage parents to get involved with their children's use of the internet and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating.

Your right to access the information: At any time, you can ask us for a copy of the personal information that we hold about you or request a correction or deletion of information.

External links: There are links on this web site that take you to other web sites outside of our service. Any links provided to third party web sites outside of this site are provided solely for your convenience. The operation and content of such third party web sites is beyond our control, and we do not endorse in any manner whatsoever or accept any responsibility for the content or other material that may be contained on such web sites, the use of such web sites, or any products or services advertised on or sold through any such web sites. We will not be liable under any circumstances for any damages whatsoever, direct or indirect, resulting from any use of this web site or any other third party web site linked to this web site, whether or not we are advised of the possibility of such damages.

While using WEO web sites, you may be exposed to content of other users. If you think any content posted on WEO web sites violates someone else's copyright or in any other way violates any law, please notify us with details so we can investigate the situation. Please contact us online or write to: Abuse Department, World Environmental Organization, 2020 Pennsylvania Ave. NW, #2001, Washington, DC 20006

Children's Guidelines: WEO complies fully with the Children�s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). None of the web sites covered by this policy knowingly collect identifiable personal information from children under age 13. If we discover that a person under the age of 13 has provided us with any personally identifiable information, we will delete that information from our systems. We are unable to reply to information requests from children under the age of 13, if so identified. A parent or guardian must initiate any requests for information from children under the age of 13 on their behalf. We encourage parents to supervise children when they browse the Internet.

Spam: WEO complies fully with the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (CAN-SPAM Act). To this end, WEO: Always offers recipients of e-mail marketing and e-newsletters a clear means of opting-out from the receipt of future messages; always includes WEO�s physical address within the body of all our e-mail messages; never uses false or misleading header information in any e-mail message; never attempts to deceive e-mail recipients by using deceptive subject lines; never uses automated means to harvest e-mail addresses from web sites or web services; never generates e-mail addresses using programmatic methods; never shares e-mail addresses with any other organizations.

Questions? WEO welcomes comments and questions on this policy. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information, and will make every reasonable effort to keep that information secure. If you have any questions, please contact us online, call us toll-free anytime at 1-800-800-2SUN, or write to:

Privacy Policy Department  
World Environmental Organization  
2020 Pennsylvania Ave. NW, #2001  
Washington, DC 20006  
Email: [privacypolicy@world.org](mailto:privacypolicy@world.org)

Last revised: August 1, 2007

This website is monitored by Service Uptime: [Free website monitoring service](http://www.serviceuptime.com/ "ServiceUptime.com - website monitoring service")
